americastestkitchen.com 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Corporate Pages

Effective: August, 2019

We at America's Test Kitchen and our related brands, including Cook's Illustrated and Cook's Country (collectively, “ATK”), are committed to respecting your privacy. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you of how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information when you visit our websites. This policy discloses the privacy practices for americastestkitchen.com, cooksillustrated.com, cookscountry.com, onlinecookingschool.com, americastestkitchenfeed.com, and the Cook’s Illustrated and Cook's Country iPad Apps, and applies only to users accessing these websites and Apps from the United States. This Policy also applies to information we collect from registrants and participants over the age of 13 through and in our ATK Kids website at americastestkitchen.com/kids/grownups.  All of our adult sites and apps are referred to collectively as the “Sites.” All of our Sites are targeted to users and individuals located in the United States.

If you are accessing this Policy from our ATK Kids site at amercastestkitchen.com/kids/home, please see our [America's Test Kitchen Kids privacy policy](https://www.americastestkitchen.com/guides/corporate-pages/america-s-test-kitchen-kids-privacy-policy).

Our Policy provides the following information:

  * Collection of Personal Information
  * Use of Information about You
  * Public Forums
  * Security
  * Business Transactions
  * California Residents
  * Changes in this Privacy Statement
  * Kids and Parents
  * Contacting Us

## COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify a single person.

There are times when we may collect personal information from you. For example, when you register with ATK for one of our websites, cooking courses, electronic newsletters, product giveaways, surveys, or other services, personal information is requested. Furthermore, you may be asked, when entering personal information into one of our third party hosted applications (our iPad App as an example), whether you agree to have information shared with ATK. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit parts of our websites and use our Apps, but you may be unable to access certain content, offers, and services. In addition we may receive information from third parties, including demographic information on site visitors (age, gender, and interests). Also, third parties may collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use our websites. We (or third party service providers on our behalf) may set and access cookies and similar technologies on your computer. The information collected may include, without limitation, information regarding your computer or device, browser, connection speed, geographic location of your computer, or other device, as well as date/time stamp, IP address, pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, the site(s), application(s), destination(s), and/or service(s) you arrived from, and other clickstream data. If you don’t want cookies, most Web browsers include an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of our sites may not function as intended.

The Do Not Track browser setting

Some Internet browsers include the ability to transmit Do Not Track signals. Our websites do not process or respond to Do Not Track signals. To learn more about “Do Not Track”, please visit [All About Do Not Track](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

## USE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

ATK uses the information we collect from site visitors in part to understand site usage and control the content and offerings on our sites or present offerings across third party sites.

From time to time, we are approached by companies or organizations that have a product or service that we believe might be of interest to you. We may share some of your information with these companies so that they can communicate their products or services to you (we never share telephone or credit card numbers with any third party). 

You may opt-out of our sharing or selling your information by contacting us at [customerservice@americastestkitchen.com](mailto:customerservice@americastestkitchen.com).

Your email address is added to our electronic mailing list so that, from time to time, we can send you our newsletters or information about special promotions. You may unsubscribe from our newsletters and marketing materials through the “unsubscribe” function in our emails or by changing your preferences in your account.

Email addresses registered to our TV show websites are sometimes shared with third party underwriters of our television shows. Registrants have the opportunity to opt-out of any third party communications at the time that they register. Email addresses registered to CooksIllustrated.com are not shared with third parties.

From time to time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). We may use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic or personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), or to send participants an email newsletter. If we use this information for other purposes, we will let you know at the time we provide the opportunity to participate in the contest or survey.

## PUBLIC FORUMS

Some of our sites may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. If you use a bulletin board or chat room on our sites, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

ATK reserves its rights to terminate the accounts of visitors who use these services in any manner inconsistent with ATK’s rules, practices, or policies, as determined in ATK’s sole discretion.

Content posted in these public forums becomes the sole property of ATK. ATK reserves the right to use content posted in these public forums for business purposes including, but not limited to, inclusion in publications and marketing.

## SECURITY

The security of your personal information is important to us. Our sites have reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, and all orders are communicated to us via a secure server. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our sites, you can send an email to us at [security@americastestkitchen.com](mailto:security@americastestkitchen.com).

## BUSINESS TRANSITIONS

In the event ATK  or any of its divisions or affiliates goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

## CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) provides our customers who are California residents with certain rights relating to their personal data.  California residents may contact us at any time to exercise the following rights: (i) to opt-out of allowing us to sell their personal information, (ii) to require that we delete their personal information from our marketing archives, and (iii) to receive a disclosure from us of how we have used their personal information and with whom we have shared it for marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and wish to exercise any of your rights under the CCPA, please send a request by email to [cap](mailto:caprivacy@americastestkitchen.com)[caprivacy@americastestkitchen.com](mailto:caprivacy@americastestkitchen.com).

## CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, by means of a notice on our home page, or through notice posted other places we deem appropriate.

## KIDS AND PARENTS

ATK’s sites, except for ATK Kids home page at americastestkitchen.com/kids/home, are not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information via any ATK site from visitors in this age group. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose to Web sites.

For information about our America's Test Kitchen Kids pages, please see the [America's Test Kitchen Kids privacy policy](https://www.americastestkitchen.com/guides/corporate-pages/america-s-test-kitchen-kids-privacy-policy).  

## CONTACTING AMERICA'S TEST KITCHEN

We are committed to privacy, and we support current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. If you have any comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [customerservice@americastestkitchen.com](mailto:customerservice@americastestkitchen.com) or:

America's Test Kitchen   
Customer Service   
21 Drydock Avenue, 2nd Floor

Boston, MA 02210   
617-232-1000

We will address any issue to the best of our abilities.

For more details about web pages for children, please see the [separate privacy policy notice](https://www.americastestkitchen.com/guides/corporate-pages/america-s-test-kitchen-kids-privacy-policy) for America's Test Kitchen Kids pages.
